Communications Workers of America (CWA), Local 1104, Operators and Service Employees; Records apap121
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action, 1950-1998 (Bulk 1989-1992); Undated; 2; 2.0 cubic ft.
  - Mobilization-- Inside Tactic Ideas, 1992; 1995 (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 7)
  - Mobilization Steering Committee, 1997 (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 8)
  - News Clips, 1989 Strike, 1989 June-1989 September (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 9)
  - News Clips, 1989 Strike, 1989 September-1989 December; 1990; Undated (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 10)
  - News Clips, Letters to the Editor About 1989 Strike, Undated (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 11)
  - News Clips, Strike-Related Court and Police Activity, 1989; Undated (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 12)
  - NYNEX Mobilization '95, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 13)
  - NYNEX Mobilization, 1997; Undated (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 14)
  - NYT Mobilization, 1993; 1995-1996; Undated (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 15)
  - Original Contract NYT '89, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 16-17)
  - Picketing Workers Photographs, 1992 (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 18)
  - Rainfare Picket, Wisconsin, Photographs, 1989 (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 19)
  - Revised Wage Progression Schedules, 1984-1985; 1987-1988; 1990-1992 (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 20)
  - Scab Answering Machine Messages, Undated (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 21)
  - Scabs--Loans '86 - [RESTRICTED], 1985; 1987-1992; Undated (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 22)
  - Solidarity Rally and Strike Photographs, Undated (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 23)
  - Strike Pictures, Oneonta, Glenn Falls, 2000 (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 24)
  - Strike '89 - [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990; Undated (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 25-26)
  - Strike '89 Disciplinary Cases - [RESTRICTED], 1987; 1990; 1992 (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 27)
  - Strike '89 Sup. Return to Work - [RESTRICTED], 1989; 1991; Undated (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 28)
  - Strike Analysis, 1986; Undated (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 29)
  - Strike Flyers & Chants, 1989; Undated (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 30)
  - Strike-Related Materials--Donna Conroy, 1989; 1992 (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 31)
  - Striking Workers Portrait, 2000 (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 32)
  - Suspensions from 1989 Strike - [RESTRICTED], 1990; Undated (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 33-36)
  - T.T.U. Bargaining Photographs, 1997 (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 37)
  - Wage Addendums, 1984-1985 (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 38)
  - Wage Reopening Agreements, 1962; 1965 (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 39)
  - Western Strike Photographs, 1989 (Box 2 (2-Contracts, Agreements, and Related Legal Action), Folder 40)
- Correspondence, 1986-1999; Undated; 3; 9.4 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically, then alphabetically within each year.
  The union kept its letters and memos according to those whose origins were national and those whose origins were local. Therefore, this series is divided into national and local subseries with folder titles retained exactly as the TTUU named them. Both subseries are arranged by year, then alphabetically by folder title within each year. The national subseries contains substantial incoming and outgoing correspondence from specific offices or people such as James Irvine (CWA vice-president) and Morton Bahr (CWA president) or presidents of locals in District One, which covers unions in New York, New Jersey, New England, and eastern Canada. The local subseries tend to be divided by group affiliation such as NYTel workers, stewards, and AT&T headquarters.
  - Local Correspondence, 1987-1998; 3.1
    - AT&T Communications, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 1)
    - CWA Communications, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 2)
    - NYT Communications, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 3)
    - Other Communications, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 4-6)
    - AT&T Stewards, 1988 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 7-8)
    - CWA Communications, Undated (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 9)
    - NYT Communications, 1988 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 10-11)
    - All Stewards, 1989 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 12)
    - AT&T Communications, 1989 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 13)
    - CWA Communications, 1989 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 14)
    - NYT Communications, 1989 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 15)
    - NYT Stewards, 1989 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 16)
    - AT&T Communications, 1990 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 17)
    - CWA Communications, 1990 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 18)
    - NYT Communications, 1990 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 19-20)
    - Other Communications, 1990 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 1)
    - All Stewards, 1991 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 2)
    - AT&T Communications, 1991 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 3-4)
    - CWA Communications, 1991 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 5)
    - NYT Communications, 1991 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 6-7)
    - NYT Communications/Joann Lyons File, 1991 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 8)
    - Other Communications, 1991 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 9)
    - All Stewards Communications, 1992 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 10)
    - AT&T Communications, 1992 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 11-12)
    - CWA Communications, 1992 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 13)
    - NYT Communications, 1992 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 14-15)
    - Other Communications, 1992 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 16)
    - All Stewards, 1993 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 17)
    - AT&T Communications, 1993 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 18)
    - AT&T Stewards, 1993 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 19-20)
    - CWA Communications, 1993 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 21)
    - CWA Grievances, 1993 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 22)
    - NYT Communications, 1993 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 23)
    - NYT Stewards, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 1-2)
    - Other Communications, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 3-4)
    - All Stewards, 1994 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 5)
    - CWA Communications, 1994 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 6)
    - NYT Stewards, 1994 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 7-8)
    - Other Communications, 1994 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 9)
    - All Stewards, 1995 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 10)
    - AT&T Members, 1995 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 11-12)
    - NYT Stewards, 1995 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 13)
    - Other Communications, 1995; 1996; 1997 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 14)
    - All Stewards, 1996 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 15)
    - CWA Communications, 1996 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 16)
    - Executive Board, 1996 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 17-22)
    - NYNEX Communications, 1996 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 1)
    - Other Communications, 1996 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 2)
    - All Stewards, 1997 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 3-4)
    - AT&T Communications, 1997 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 5)
    - CWA Communications, 1997 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 6)
    - Executive Board, 1997 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 7-12)
    - NYNEX Communications, 1997 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 13-14)
    - Other Communications, 1997 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 15)
    - Executive Board, 1998 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 16-21)
    - Bell Atlantic, 1998 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 1)
    - CWA Grievances, 1998 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 2)
    - Other Communications, 1998 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 3)
    - Stewards, 1998 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 4-5)
  - National Correspondence, 1986-1999; 3.2
    - CWA, 1986 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 1)
    - CWA Communications, 1986 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 2-3)
    - Local Presidents, 1986 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 4-6)
    - CWA Communications, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 7-9)
    - Local Presidents, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 10-12)
    - CWA Communications, 1988 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 13)
    - District One, 1988 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 14)
    - Irvine -- AT&T, 1988 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 15-16)
    - Local Presidents (1 of 3), 1988 (Box 1 (3-Correspondence), Folder 17)
    - Local Presidents (2-3 of 3), 1988 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 1-2)
    - District One, 1989 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 3-4)
    - Irvine -- AT&T, 1989 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 5-6)
    - Local Presidents, 1989 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 7-9)
    - District One, 1990 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 10-13)
    - Irvine's Office, 1990 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 14-16)
    - Local Presidents, 1990 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence), Folder 17-18)
    - District One, 1991 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 1-3)
    - Irvine's Office, 1991 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 4-6)
    - Local Presidents, 1991 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 7-8)
    - District One, 1992 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 9-10)
    - Irvine's Office, 1992 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 11-13)
    - Local Presidents, 1992 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence), Folder 14-16)
    - Bahr--Public Relations Incident, 1993 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 1)
    - District One, 1993 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 2-3)
    - Irvine's Office, 1993 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 4-8)
    - Local Presidents, 1993 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 9-11)
    - District One, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 12-13)
    - Irvine's Office, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence), Folder 14-18)
    - Local Presidents, 1994 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 1-2)
    - District One, 1995 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 3-6)
    - Irvine's Office, 1995 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 7-9)
    - Local Presidents, 1995 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 10-11)
    - District One, 1996 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 12-13)
    - Irvine's Office, 1996 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 14-16)
    - Local Presidents, 1996 (Box 5 (3-Correspondence), Folder 17-18)
    - Mancino, 1996 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 1-2)
    - District One, 1997 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 3-4)
    - Local Presidents, 1997 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 5-10)
    - Mancino, 1997 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 11-12)
    - Other Correspondence, 1997 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 13-17)
    - AT&T: Irvine, Brown, and Grimes, 1998 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 18)
    - AT&T: Other Correspondence, 1998 (Box 6 (3-Correspondence), Folder 19)
    - District One: Maher, Martini and Master, 1998 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 1)
    - District One: Dolan and Other, 1998 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 2)
    - Local Presidents: Baher and Easterling, 1998 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 3)
    - Local Presidents: Nichols and Other, 1998 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 4)
    - Mancino, 1998 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 5)
    - Other Correspondence, 1998 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 6-8)
    - AT&T: Irvine, Klimm, Brown, Grimes and Other, 1999 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 9)
    - District One: Wooda (Asst.'t to V.P) and Maher (Area Director), 1999 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 10)
    - District One: Maher cont.'d -A-, 1999 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 11)
    - District One: Maher cont.'d -B-, 1999 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 12)
    - District One: Miller, Hayes and Other, 1999 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 13)
    - Local Presidents: Bahr and Easterling, 1999 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 14)
    - Local Presidents: Cohen and Other, 1999 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 15)
    - Mancino, 1999 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 16)
    - Mancino--Charges, 1999 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 17)
    - Other Correspondence, 1999 (Box 7 (3-Correspondence), Folder 18-19)
- Subject Files, 1949-1999 (Bulk 1983-1997); Undated; 4; 3.2 cubic ft.
  The bulk of the files in this series date from the 1980s and 1990s and belonged to Kim Young, executive vice president of Local 1112, with a smaller number of files originating from the office of the local's president Donna Conroy. The material documents ongoing union business, the local union's relations with AT&T and management, and day-to-day issues affecting unionized offices and members. Also included are efforts to prevent office closures and programs to assist union members when management decided to close offices. Other materials of interest are employee petitions, major company and union initiatives such as the "Safe Workplace Campaign"" which addressed ergonomic challenges faced by operators, and a run of the union's official newsletter, Traffic Calls, including its debut issue in 1949.
  - 10th Annual E. Gerald Horgan Labor Award, 1999 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - 2+ Meeting, March 21, 1999, 1991-1993; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Ad-Hoc Meeting Minutes, 1989-1991; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Ad-Hoc Meeting Minutes, 1992-1993; 1996-1998; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - The Alliance for Employee Growth and Development, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - The Alliance for Employee Growth and Development, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - American Family Celebration Photographs, 1988 May (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Ant- Automated Rally, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Arbitration Awards, Photographs, 1984 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - AT&T Awards, 1984-1994 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Awarding of Department of Correction Contract to MCI, 1989; 1991 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Buffalo Meeting Photographs, 1976 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Departmental Meeting, Cherry Hill, NJ, Photographs, 1979 October (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Buffalo Directory Assistance Office, Possible Closure, 1991; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Constructive Relationship Meeting, 1990; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Dues, 1992; 1993; 1997 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Dues, 1997; 1998 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Ergonomics Program (AT&T), 1993; 1994; 1997 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Ergonomics Program Conference '97, 1997 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Flyer: "Stop the AT&Tack on my Job! No I without Operators", Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Gotham Appraisal, 1992-1994; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Handwritten History of Telephone Traffic Union Upstate, New York, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Jesse Jackson Campaign Rally Photographs, 1988 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Jobs with Justice Rally Photographs, ca. 1980s (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Jobs with Justice Rally- Buffalo, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Joint Meetings Upstate Unions, Photographs, 1980 April 16 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Labor Day Photographs, 1987 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Lucent Spin-off and Restructuring, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Meeting Photographs, 1983 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Meetings with Management, 1987-1988; 1990-1992; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Meetings with Management, 1996; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Midwest Center for Labor Research, 1990; 1993 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Multi-Union Rally-Albany, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Newsclips and Press Releases, Office Closures, 1993; 1995; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - "Nickel and Diming at Spirit" CWA Cartoon, 1997 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Newsletters, Clifton Park NY Relay Center Times-Picayune, 1995; 1996 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Newsletters, New York Generator, 1989 NYNEX Strike, 1999 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Newsletters Traffic Calls, 1949-1958 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Newsletters Traffic Calls, 1959-1971 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, Union Connections, 1988 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Newsletter, The United Independents of Upstate New York, 1974 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Office Photographs, General, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Offices, Albany, Gas Odor '92, 1992; 1994 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Offices, Albany OSPS Survey, 1992-1994 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Offices, Amherst, 1989; 1991; 1993 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Offices, Binghamton Closing, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Offices, Binghamton, Operator Expectations, 1993; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Offices, Binghamton, TEI, 1990-1992 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Offices, Buffalo, TEI, 1991; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Offices, Clifton Park, 1989; 1992-1994; 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Offices, Clifton Park OSHA 200 Logs, 1991-1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Offices, Clifton Park Safe Workplace Campaign, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Offices, Clifton Park Safe Workplace Campaign, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Offices, Clifton Park TEI, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Offices, Clifton Park TEI, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Offices, Clifton Park UDT Repetitive Motion Illness Survey, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Offices, Clifton Park UDT Surveys, 1992; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Offices, Clifton Park, UDT Surveys, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Offices, Colonie TEI, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Offices, Corning TEI, 1991; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Offices, Schenectady, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Offices, Syracuse, 1990; 1992; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Offices, Syracuse, CAG Info, 1991; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Offices, Syracuse SPEE Offer, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Offices, Syracuse/Utica Task Force Committee Minutes, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Offices, Utica, 1990-1994 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Organizing Materials, 1987-1988; 1990-1993; 1999-2000; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - OSPS, 1986-1988 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - OSPS, 1988-1989 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - OSPS, 1989-1991; 1993; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - OSPS Handbook, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - OSPS Handbook, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Parade Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Petitions, Air Purifier, 1983; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Petitions, Challenge to Election of Representative, 1985 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Petitions, Combining Seniority Lists, 1987 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Petitions, Demand for Affiliation Ballot, 1985 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Petitions, Demand for Departmental Representative, 1985; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Petitions, Disagreement with Day Union Meeting, 1983 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Petitions, Disagreement with necessary Service Assistant Qualifications, 1985 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Petitions, Disgust with Lack of Union Representation, Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Petitions, Lack of Represenation by President Dawson, Local 212, 1983 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Petitions, Manual Selection of Holiday Hours, Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Petitions, Parking Area In Syracuse, 1984 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Petitions, Possible Affiliation with AESCME, 1984 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Petitions, Reminder to Executive against communication Abuse, 1986 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Petitions, Seniority for Vacation Weeks, 1983 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Petitions, Sunday Scheduling, Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Petitions, Support S. 1776/A. 2640 Anti-Bugging Legislations, Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Quality of Worklife AT&T, 1988-1991 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Reengineering Conference, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Reengineering Conference, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Rochester Council for Occupational Safety and Health, Photographs, 1979 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Shares for Growth, 1994; 1996-1997 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Strategy Meeting AT&T, January 14-15, 1991, 1990-1991; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Surplus, 1986; 1993-1997; 1999 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Surplus Declarations, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Surplus Options, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Surplus Options, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Surplus Options, 1995-1996 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - TEI, 1985-1990 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - TEI, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - TEI, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - TEI, 1992; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - TEI, Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - TEI, Facilitator Role, 1990-1992; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - UCAT, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - UCAT, 1995-1997 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Uniform Operating Practices Manual, Replaced Pages, 1968; 1972; 1975-1978; 1980; 1987-1990 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Uniform Operating Practices Manual, Replaced Pages, 1988 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - VDT Surveys, 1996; Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - United Way, 1991; 1996 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
- Conventions and Seminars, 1978-2000; 5; 3.4 cubic ft.